A Guide to the Executive Office Congressional E-Commerce Commission Files for Governor James S. Gilmore, 1999-2000
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Executive Office Congressional E-Commerce Commission Files for Governor James S. Gilmore, 1999-2000
The Library of Virginia
40176
1.0 cu. ft. (1 box)
Virginia. Governor (1998-2002: Gilmore)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from James S. Gilmore, 11/17/2002.
Historical Information
The Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce was established in 1998 by the United States Congress to study "federal, state and local, and international taxation and tariff treatment of transactions using the Internet and Internet access and other comparable intrastate, interstate or international sales activities." Governor James S. Gilmore, III chaired the Commission.
Scope and Content
The Commission met in four major meetings: Williamsburg, Virginia (1999 June 21-22), New York City, New York (1999 September 14-15), San Francisco, California (1999 December 14-15), and Dallas, Texas (2000 March 20-21). The Commission submitted its' Report to Congress in April 2000. This series includes Governor James S. Gilmore's copies of the briefing, agenda and presentations for these meetings as well as a draft copy of the Commission's Report to Congress.
Contents List
- Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (part one) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (part two) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Briefing and Agenda of Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (part three) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Index of Presentation Material, Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Presentation Material of Andrew Pincus, Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (empty) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Presentation Material of Peter R. Merrill, Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Presentation Material of Joseph Guttentag, Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (empty) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Presentation Material of Donald S. Abelson, Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Presentation Material of William F. Fox, Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Presentation Material of Walter Hellerstein, Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Presentation Material of Charles E. McLure, Jr., Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Presentation Material of Orson Swindle, Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 June 21-22, Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 September 14-15, New York City, New York (part one) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 September 14-15, New York City, New York (part two) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Proposal by Global Crossing, Ltd submitted to E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce, 1999 November 15 (part one) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Proposal by Global Crossing, Ltd submitted to E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce, 1999 November 15 (part two) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 December 14-15, San Francisco, California (part one) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 1999 December 14-15, San Francisco, California (part two) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Briefing and Agenda of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Meeting, 2000 March 20-21, Dallas, Texas (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Draft of E-Commerce Advisory Commission on Electronic Commerce Report to Congress, 2000 April (Box 1, Folder 20)